From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight, truce,
Trolls be dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stoppin'
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marbles fan from above
It's like the Awake has stepped in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so big play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like the Awake has don't look away
Your shadow's talkin', it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
Got some subway trying to pack this tobacco. How are you guys?
Oh
Hi Christine, how are you?
Good to see you. Hi everybody. Oh
Look how clean my place is today. Well tables a little messy, but look
Hey, thank you for gifting the membership Christine. Thank you so much. Thank you guys
Let me see I
Like to match those sometimes too
Thank you Christine
How's everybody? I was uh, yeah, I went to um pebs show last night
I was on for a little bit with diamond
It was good
Save to watch later
So who won that uh that membership that was uh?
Amber oh congratulations
Hey amber. I love when people that I know
Get a membership
I'm gonna keep it going too
Supposedly it said like you know they give away like five memberships a month or something or ten members or something but
The memberships that they give away are here we go. Thank you. Oh
Oh, I know I know ridiculous Chris isn't he ridiculous?
I know and ashes to ashes. We got amber and ashes to ashes receive some memberships today. I
Love it give I love a good giveaway
Do you know who ashes to ashes is that a good person? Oh
Yeah, yeah, and yeah, I heard all the ridiculous stuff being talked about I mean just so ridiculous
Thank you guys. I'm gonna just give a little thank you to the chat. Hope you enjoy these
Hurricane paro you've received a membership. I do hope I do see some of these hurricane paro has been in here recently
Yeah, oh
Yeah, gotcha gotcha
Hey, traveling gypsy good to see you
How are you doing good guy good to see everybody I
Have I just had a tuna sandwich from Subway. I have some coffee left
It's pretty good
Yeah, so guys tiktok of 706 subscribers or you know
Followers right now
You know, I do have like the
And TikTok you can get pretty much monetized within a few days as soon as I I
Think I got how many subscribers did I have and I got monetized
I think all I had to do was broadcast three days in a row and then I
Was monetized let's do a general out of this deck. I love this this gold deck
Okay, it's a great deck. This was a gift from Amanda Erickson
Okay, let's see what we got five of wands, so this is like a friendly competition
Sometimes it's considered a you know a little bit of a fight
But I think it's more of a friendly competition when it's upright like that five of wands
That kind of looks like they're playing a game
What else do we got?
Two of wands to so we got a lot of passion involved in here and two of wands you're waiting for something here ships to come in
You got the world in your hands. You're looking over the ocean
Okay, Christine. Love you. Thank you so much. I hope you feel better. Hi, Christine. If you feel better, I'll do five cards today
Do you got five of wands two of wands and we got the queen of wands? Okay?
Definitely in this this passion of energy, right but under control. I love you Christine. Hope you feel better
Love the little her little black cat there. He's a little black cat watching her. Hey, man
There's two more cards and I'll get a some more good advice
Page of pentacles so somebody bringing something to you that can grow into something bigger an idea a seed
Look out for this opportunity
Maybe a younger person involved for giving you this idea
Okay, it's a page pages are usually younger people and finally
Mean the tower is not that great to get but it can be a sudden shake-up. So maybe that
Will be in a good way. I'll get you a couple words of advice
We have the Sun just be happy be positive stay positive, you know, the Sun will come out the Sun is shining on you
I think that really will make that tower
Tower and its best best energy
Okay
Yeah, we got
We got the happiness and but also just like
Also, if you are sad about something, you know, this can meet tears. It kind of looks like tears a little bit
But tempered with the Sun
You're gonna be able to get over everything I'll tool a little more card
Just say I know people are carrying these burdens for other people and you put those down
Put those down you'll have to carry everybody's burdens or just maybe rearrange them a little bit put a bit
Their fans out like that it can be more cumbersome put them all in a little bundle
Put it over your head. Okay. I hope you guys like that. Hey, Ilya
Hi everybody
So
I'm the waiting for a friend to come over he's not texting. Hey Vicky. How are you?
Hi everybody moving at you stress you got a little high. Yeah, I got a my uh
Get my vape around here someplace. I'm gonna hit in a minute
Some text message real quick
Oh
So how was your Friday almost went to the pier today
But
Okay
You're killing it quick though with getting out these things and packing good stuff. What are you doing? You're moving?
Yeah
Well, I did all my laundry. I cleaned my house. I vacuumed. I got a new vacuum cleaner
It's Red Dress Friday. I
Did it all for the nukie. What the biscuit is that a biscuit joke Ilya you're doing biscuit jokes, too. Oh, no
It's okay, I don't mind
Yeah, so guys, I want to tell you this thing about chat GPT. There's a video I found it's like how to program it to like
Your specifications, I don't know if you have to have the upgraded chat GPT
I do have a plus, you know, it's not not pro. It's plus
So I get to use the
the new
valet I think it's called a valet
Or no, it's called agent. It's called the agent. Okay. It's called chat GPT agent
What agent can do is they take over it has its own computer to use and so it can like if you say
Oh, book me these plane reservations. I can pay for them and stuff like that
It can do this kind of stuff a little bit like every time I've typed into it. It doesn't work, but
This guy gave these like seven questions
You can like get it to jet chat GPT will generate these seven questions. You just have to copy paste this thing into the
into the, you can basically program chat GPPT, you say,
okay, imagine you are, you know, a YouTube,
professional YouTube streamer,
and that will come up with kind of that mindset.
But yeah, so basically I got it to ask these seven questions
which I answered, and then that's,
now it's gonna be more to my specifications.
It's a really cool, cool program.
It is free.
Go ahead and try a TriChat GPT.
I'm working with it a lot on some of the AI music,
the lyrics, song lyrics.
It's very, very, very, very good.
Uh-oh.
OK.
So I hope everyone's feeling good today.
I'm just gonna finish this coffee off.
I hope it doesn't have a sandwich.
Mm, that was good.
Subway sandwich, coffee.
You're a big fan of AI good.
I mean, it's like some people a bit say,
oh no, no, it's like, it is fast.
But it's just that there's things I would never be able to do like I'm I'm a good I
Think I have good concepts for the songs, but
AI is really good at putting in the concept into like a workable
Creation then I put it through another
AI music generator, and I've also been doing a couple, you know, I can make a couple videos too
pretty expensive
To make
Can you help you with your your audio? Can you try to help you with your audio? Sure
Yeah, let me I can I can tell you the
Website I use if you want to do some music to your lyrics if you wrote the lyrics yourself or if you generated them
I think it's called. I'll get it for you once they get called. Here we go
You're glad it's there. Yeah, I'm glad it's there too. I mean it's like
It just allows me to be creative without having to be at beyond genius levels of talent and creativity.
I don't play instruments, but let me see.
So here is the website I use. This is free.
But unless you upgrade, it won't allow you to...
To save the music I mean it's until like I'm you know save it on to your own file and use it as you want
I have the upgraded but there you go. That is the
That is a music generator. I use if you'd like to
experiment with your own songs that I'll even
Consider sharing on you know, you'd like to make a song with kind of the theme of the show or something like that
I'd be happy to
to listen to them and stuff.
So that's a really cool site though.
And you just basically just take the lyrics.
You can have lyrics generated.
You just put up some prompts of what the song about
into chat GPT.
It'll come out with lyrics, copy paste the lyrics,
put it into this generator,
and it will put in the style you want.
There's a lot of options for that.
And then,
It will create the song in the style you specify within a few minutes and then if you have the upgraded thing, I think it's like 10 bucks or maybe a little bit more, maybe 20 bucks upgrades, you'll get like, I think maybe a thousand credits a month, which is like, I think like, at least a few hundred songs, you know, so I have plenty of, plenty of space to go.
Yeah, I've uh
That it's nice to be in a clean house, but it's kind of like what do I do now? What do I do now, right?
Hey juice, how are you?
Hi KZ. How are you?
I don't know.
I need to figure out if anybody's in Purgatory,
which is Emma's Discord server.
And if there's some former mod in there,
you can let me know who that is.
I've been told about it.
I thought it was KZ, but I guess it's not.
You can tell me who is, keep on cleaning.
Yeah.
I guess there is always more to do.
You can always like start, I can say,
hey J-Dog, I will.
You can see.
My table is relatively clean. It's a little bit messy
But you got all my laundry done
I got a I like this vacuum. I got a lot. It's pretty cool
Yeah, guys, how are we doing tonight?
Hopefully we're gonna have a great night. Let me get my glasses on
See my I'm seeing a little bit clearer today. I can read actually read the
the screen today
my eyes have
improved
Can actually read
Remember my vision was all blurry for the past few weeks. I don't know why
Hi kid bilbas bilbas
Are you bulbous sack? I
Don't know now your kid bulbous. Well, welcome everybody
You can have a little chat tonight here Nancy. How are you? I love your avatar
So anyway, I
Do like tick-tock I just been spending a little bit much on like gifts
So what I've now what I'm trying to do is not give too many gifts
Like I was you know, I would try it but I can at least give like a it's called the heart me
Anna on it, and it's like it seems like if people really like that gift. I'm feeling better. I'm feeling good
I've slept a lot today
I just had a coffee. I just had most of the sandwich. I feel pretty good. I
Didn't even finish all my beers last night
I got the stream yard link up come say hi to me. I'll pin the link on my
Thing I did give a couple of memberships away today and
Christine did thank you so much
Okay
Get here
YouTube. Hi guys.
Yeah, I saw it went and said side of summer.
Okay, I'm good.
Yeah, I know I did read yesterday we had a little a message from Mirna.
About Michael and it was a very sweet message. I have to find where that message is so I can reply to it because I do want her to come and
maybe talk to the chat and
You know, I don't know exactly what happened to the situation, but
Also guys, I got so many of these
Of these episodes are now on
Private or members only
So if you are a member you can see a lot of the past episodes
I do just put them on members only for the safety of the show basically, but
Okay, I'm doing good. How are you guys doing me interesting today?
Oh, that's just pure tobacco now. Let me see if I can get here
Got
There we go
also, I was able to get my
Electric razor I've ordered like the replacement part. I didn't think it fit, but it does fit
So I think it's charging my electric razor
Finally, I have that fixed good news
You you narrowed your entire head today. Oh, I want to see that though you narrowed it
Is it kind of sting I remember I used to like you know when I was like a teenager. I would near my face sometimes and
It would sting a little bit my
There we go, I don't know it was really weird like if people are saying really rude stuff today like recently about
You know me's having some kind of disease. I do not have a disease. I am absolutely fine. I'm healthy
Probably healthier than a lot of people
So do not worry about ridiculous things people say
Yeah, but I'd like to see that J-dog
Yeah, but like I said 700 people on tiktok now followers once I get to a thousand
I'll be able to get to the next level of the monetization there
I think there's a couple programs I can enjoy and then then basically after that I need to get to 10,000
And I will do that. I will do that because it is easier to
Get you know follow people there. They follow you back rather than on YouTube
You have to like you know people have to find your channel subscribe to your channel and
so anyway
Yeah, so I did just
Hit this vape and I'm hide again
It doesn't put me asleep. It's gonna be asleep like three times today. I've taken three naps. I
Don't like to keep falling asleep
Okay, so let me like
Join this thing on Timu today. It was like the Timu like monthly
It was basically for three months for free. I got you know, I
Don't know if it's
Will save me anything. Have you seen this the Timu stuff? It's like you win always win every deal. You're you're on your way
Okay
We have a look if I have Timu on this tablet, yeah, I do
Hey, so like can you hear me? Yeah, how are you? Oh, hi Jim, brother
Not too bad not too bad
Good to see you ever told me did you ever get to buy your computer or not? Well, you know
The YouTube pays out once a month. And so it's not the day yet. And so it will you know, I feel like dude
I paid you a lot of money, but you know, I've had a lot of money too is you too
We're a lot of what's the percentage of the tax they they take them they take a little bit
I think they might take like 25 to 30 percent, but the thing is
It is I do have a cash up to but the thing with YouTube is that I didn't know that when I was doing
But you know, it's it's okay because YouTube probably
Improve me in the algorithm like it probably sort of promoting my show more because it it does get a piece of that
So it has a kind of more incentive to promote and stuff. And so I think that
I think it's good to you know Emma always just would say just donate on YouTube
She's like don't send it don't send a cash up. She didn't like to mention the word cash app
She just want to mention like the YouTube monetization. I think it's a smart strategy. I don't know if they care that much
necessarily about
Right it is but I do use the platform
It is like kind of exciting when everyone sees it inside the chat pop-up
You know, it's kind of like it was exciting, you know, and it's yeah, it's a little bit
It can be a little bit of a
little bit of a chunk they take but I think
You know, it's like it's kind of like a manager YouTube's kind of like my manager in a way. It's your money, bro
However, you want to take it. It's your money
Thank you. Well, you know, it's also I think on YouTube
You know, it's like you have to
Make sure that the the stream doesn't get deleted and stuff like that like you have to make sure
Yeah, and so it can be like a little bit. That's why I have to end sometimes
After a donation like I say that and they're like, oh, you're trying to you're trying to rule
You're trying to tell psyche what he's been you're trying to rule psyche's panel
Because you gave money no, I'm sure if you show if you show something like obviously it's not okay
Yeah, I mean, I and you never broke the rule. You never broke one rule about that, you know, and it's like
I don't think I ever broke one brother. Yeah. No, you've had none for how long? Oh
Probably since I started the show
All right, well, man, maybe over a year
Yeah, definitely over a year. Yeah
There's been a thousand summer's panel and it came over. Yeah, I think it was well over a year. I
Don't know if it was well over a year
Well, it's like, yeah, because last August I think I was like starting basically the show like I think and so
It was August or September. I know for sure. I was doing episodes in October, but I was still
Remember I was crashing about you about a terror readings and shit. That was well over like a year ago
Yeah, I remember that I remember that and then it's like we were on summer spit
We were on the talk your ish and then you got
And I hate to bring it up and I'm gonna bring it up some I tell you how long we've actually been talking
You guys people were calling me Tony of all people believe it or not
Remember that I remember that was like well over it. That was well over that was
Yeah, what the fuck, but I'm not trying to bring that up on this end. It's okay. Hey, did Tony ever give you that much money?
No, Tony that Tony all Tony dude was you know, you know attack me was crash. Oh
He hates he was he was attacked me. Hey J dog. You have J dog here. Hey
Yeah, let's get what J dog join please
There he is. He was chilling. I talked to him earlier a little bit, but he was just chilling like you get really tough
If you're a few areas like you yeah, I like I like J dog J. That was a cool guy. Yeah, I like J dog
I like you guys.
You near your head, you near your head today?
Yeah, look at, look at the mirror.
It burned a little bit.
That ain't the J-Dog right now.
Looks good.
That's not cool though.
Michael Jordan.
J-Dog, are you ever on TikTok?
Are you on that website ever?
No, I got blocked off TikTok, unfortunately.
Blocked and so you can't even like make a new account or anything. No, my IP address is blocked on the device
I would have to get a different device and you can get a lot because supposedly somebody with a different account, brother
VPN my name my username, and I guess they were I
Don't know what they were doing, but they had got me bad from kick-talk, so I can't leave just talk anymore
Yeah, this ain't no J. Joe right now, but it's nice to meet you, dog
What's going on, bro? How are you doing?
Yeah, I talked to you before brother
Just killing killing man. Another day another dollar
killing
That's what's up. It goes to smoke room
Not too much anymore, brother. Okay. What do you know? I just chill in just kick it
You ever try narrow goes
Your answer we thought sorry good you ever try narrow
There yeah, like the hair removal scuffs I get on my head
But it came on
I'm also I'm also
Oh what
I'm white
I mean, I don't know how to explain to you. I'm Caucasian. Oh, okay
You're you
You're checking out summer screen earlier. She's doing that photo shoot, huh?
Yeah, were you there? Yeah, I was watching it too
Pretty cool. Well, let's get this straight though. Summer's a
Life-streaming shit. You know what I do there. I I uh debate
You know you are
Say it again. I'm sorry. I didn't hear you. I'd like to debate. I like to debate a lot
That's cool man. I'm glad you like to debate
You'd like to debate all kinds of stuff or just like debate in general and whatever you want to think of I don't fucking debate it
Let's run that bitch
Politics I don't know
I don't know one psyche
Look too controversial. Yeah, it's like he's over. I'm on psyche channel. He's obviously okay with it. Let's run that bitch yard
Oh, so what do you think about the earthquake supposedly they were supposed to be a earthquake and like a signal me
Well, the last thing I heard about was the Texas floods brother. I hear nothing about no earthquake
Unless you want to explain to me
Are that there was an earthquake in Russia?
That had happened. Well, I don't know the shock waves from Russia and Alaska wherever the fuck it's at
Comes down and that dude if it was the shockwaves reached us, you know how big that fucking
Earth we would have to be and they reached us
That's a pretty fucking. I mean anybody else here about this or?
It's just what I heard. I don't know if it's well. They say it's true. Yeah
It's on the news, but yeah, it was it was weird
So the whole entire West Coast was on a put on alert for a possible tsunami even psych psych
entire earthquake or tsunami
Yeah, so well the earthquake caused the tsunami the entire earthquake, you know, that's how it happens
Yeah, but unless it's real close to the shore, yeah
Yeah, so that's causes the tsunamis supposedly, but I didn't see no tsunami. I
Haven't seen no one inch of a tsunami anywhere. No
Where are you at ghosts are you in East Coast?
It was
Wherever you think I'm from okay, we'll say the United Kingdom
That is true
The United Kingdom so what time is it right now in the night again? It's probably like what seven eight o'clock
Want to say roughly
So dude, why are those people? Oh, we're sassy scarlet. I know sassy scarlet is from the United Kingdom also
Why do they have a day really have that like in the United Kingdom when they have like tea and crumpets and like
Fucking tea time. I'm pretty sure they do
Why though?
You know Muslims like you know about some place certain hours a day. Do you know about some of you that?
No, I'm not a Muslim
Didn't I didn't call you a Muslim dude? No, no, I know what I'm just saying
I'm not a Muslim. So I don't know their culture or their customs the fucking weird. They do that. They do that
Why I
Don't know
Then you don't know what the fuck they're doing either
Nope
Who's your favorite guest to debate on here if you had to pick one besides summer? Definitely now. Well, I like Jay
One, you know, he's from New York. I like these New York motherfuckers
Now see I do I do love summer. I like these New York motherfuckers and pretty much anybody that wants it besides you
You kind of retard it
No, I'm not retarded
Well, you're kind of stupid, sir
No, I'm not going stupid. I'm the opposite of stupid. I'm well
You're the opposite of stupid opposite of stupid. Yes. Yes
Prove that go ahead
Exit back a hundred percent effect, you know, I'm professional. Why are you gonna prove you're gonna so good?
I'm professional race car driver. Did you know that? I have I have a license
I'm Michael Jordan
You're 2006
Certified
There's no one else is gonna join. I don't know
Where's everybody at?
And I'm not down you brother you you're right a all power to you brother one of them
I'm punished fuck so half of the sheena coming in
You know who you know who J dog knows is he knows Tony?
No, I know J dog from
New York, I don't know this shade
This is bad is this L.A. new dog. This is yeah, I'm the calmer
La
Yeah, oh
I was telling him about
We the West Coast the entire West Coast line was on alert for that tsunami
Yeah, I think ever happened. No, I think it was just like, you know, they do over
I don't think we got a big wave or something like that. I don't know
Whose phone ringing
We gonna answer it or not
He's answering. Oh, he said he'll be back. Did you have a good conversation with them? I sorry I had to
Take care of some business real quick
See you're blown away hearing about siestas in Europe. What but they take a nap in the afternoon
Yeah, I went to actually Spain when I was 14 and so, you know, we would we would have like a nice lunch
And drink and then we'd have a siesta like and that was like part of the culture
Everyone just takes like a nap in the afternoon
so
Yeah, hi, so what were you talking about? You're talking about the earthquakes and stuff
Hi, so Banford, so yeah, so tick-tock I have like 700
700 followers now pretty cool
Yeah
That's been in like it's only been like two weeks ago. I'm already monetized on it, too
I mean, I think maybe it's been three weeks, but I'm already monetized as well
Was there earthquake yesterday? I didn't feel it. I didn't feel it earthquake yesterday. I
Didn't I bet I was like, you know, I did sleep a lot yesterday and I was up to like a in the nighttime, but it was just calm
I had some Taco Bell last night and a couple coffees
Uh, very tasty
The cinnamon coffee. I'm gonna join. I'm gonna join. I'm gonna leave. I'll join right back. Okay. Okay. Okay. Love you
Yeah, so let me see I'll put like a little banner up. Let me see. I hope to put my I think I can put my
Let's see use this yeah
There we go, that fits perfect actually look
Electra designed this
Electra is very talented. I wish I could figure out how to do like the graphics as good as her and they
I need to bring me talk to her
And learn a little bit, but I yeah, she made this really really awesome
Awesome background. I love this cloud one
He said he got his IP ban from TikTok and then he said somebody made an account
That's why he got banned all the same breath. You see what's wrong with that. Yeah, well, it's like, I don't know
But it's like, you know, what's a weird thing to lie about, you know, some it's like I don't really like, you know
It's not really consequential to and here we go
So
Hey person, how are you?
Person I have a
Also, I got accepted into the Amazon influencer program.
And so Amazon has a good thing for influencers
where they give you a page to use
and then you can put little videos and stuff
or show products that you've got off YouTube or off Amazon.
And then you can get a commission
if people purchase them and stuff.
So basically, I got accepted to that program.
Because of my YouTube channel, I just put my YouTube through and they're like, okay, you have enough people
But I still have to put some stuff on there, but I'm gonna put reviews of my stuff
I'll show like some of the gifts I get up like that that was from Amazon from spunky spunky got that on my Amazon
Wishlist, but a beautiful alien
You see like that. You like the lighting today. It's pretty nice lighting, huh? I
Don't know. I think it's pretty cool
You're glad it's Friday. It's been a brutal week. Yeah. Well, give me two. Friday is always a nice day
I'd like I love Fridays and
Ready for the weekend. I don't know. I haven't seen Alisa on live recently. I know she was live recently, but um,
I don't know something's happening in Florida. I don't know but the Fistunami thing was affecting over there or something like that, but I
Haven't seen her go live and then she's like, oh everyone's safe. And so I'm not sure exactly what's going on in Florida. Hopefully everyone's okay
Um, yeah, so that was, uh, I don't know if you, you heard that email I got yesterday from
Myrna, but I think I'll read it again.
Um, did you hear the email?
I didn't hear it.
Okay.
Yeah.
Well, I actually, she just posted on my, I think, community board about it.
Let me see if I can find it.
Um, okay.
Uh, here's the message.
It says, Psyche, by now you probably know Michael L. passed away on July 18th.
I just wanted you to know how greatly he appreciated your-
Quote online friendship you have a great influence on people through your online channel and Michael felt loyal to you through this past
Year he would always say I want to go on panel and support psyche
He was often misunderstood for who he chose to portray himself as and he said things he shouldn't have
But in reality, he truly was a sensitive, loving, loyal guy, opinionated, and curious
about things he often questioned.
I choose to honor his memory with the good times.
I hope you and the rest of this community does as well.
I've always believed that love conquers evil.
Much peace and love to all, Myrna.
And then it says...
You didn't even get one dollar at all.
And then in Michael's quote was every day above ground is a good day Michael L
Michael Liguise among and so guys I think you can maybe look up as obituary if you want to if you want
Not even $1
One dollar for what?
Good domain. He appreciate it that much. He could donate about
Well, Michael, I don't have to do it. I mean, I don't he did
Support certain people like I do I do but I I made money
Because of Michael because he got
Um, he got a kicked off the panel, maybe like five, six, seven, eight times, uh, you know for the 24 hours. And so
Okay, I'm sorry guys guys
It's like you do you feel okay with opening up? We'd have to debate or not
Yeah, if anyone wants to come and debate ghost here's the stream yard link. I think the link is pinned
He wants to cut he wants to fight. He's in the mood to fight tonight guys if you want to talk no debate about anything
He's a he was my fight. He just wants to debate have a healthy debate, you know
Okay, however you want to do it ghost, but I mean it's like it's been a little bit quiet lately, I don't know
Let's leave it quiet
Well, anybody you want to but nobody wants to come up nobody I
Know it's like a little oh, so nobody says he will join a sweep he does so sweep he or you're gonna you're gonna
Let's run that way start
You can fight with the ghost or not fight, but you know you have a nice
nice little debate
Don't be shy
Don't be shy. Let's be nervous. We'll also don't be mean I'll be nice
It'll be nice.
Yeah, it goes promises will be nice.
So if you're a person, I wonder where.
Oh, so that was on my community wall.
I do have like, just for the members,
I do have like a members community wall.
Oh, I see your comments too.
You said, you're, you said, I see your comments.
I'm gonna have to leave.
You guys are, I'm gonna have to leave.
I'll be back.
Figured out by some of the out figured out by some of back here. Okay. I'll try yeah
You heard yeah, yeah
Say it right those no psyche
No, say it say right
Shit
There's actually a band called ghost. It's a really good band. I don't know if you've heard
Okay
Sweepy oh yard. Okay. Why E. R. D. I was thinking why you are D?
So
Yeah, let's just
And then Michael
You'll see that lower Marion high
Yeah, that's sad you heard you heard I love it
So
is everyone doing in chat?
Yeah, so it's kind of sad.
I'm doing good.
I'm sitting here chilling on psyche spin.
I'm doing pretty good, bro.
I'm good.
Yeah.
Anybody's looking.
Is that all right?
You heard?
Yes.
Yup.
Now I don't say,
I don't feel like there's anything wrong with that, Yurt.
Do you feel like there's something wrong with that?
Sorry, hello. Hello. Sorry. I'm up to 709 fall over
So what was the question?
What's your favorite band ghost, what is the favorite band?
It's a matter
I'm thinking what I asked what's your favorite band because someone says your favorite band sucks, but what's your favorite band?
Well, fuck him. Fuck your favor band. Fuck that favor band. If he wants to come over here
You bait me. I'm down to do it
Good. Okay. Lava Lava. Do you want to come up?
The link is
Actually, I'll let you I'll let you I will literally let you talk
I won't and I was and I was and I was stepped I was stepped down from the pain
I mean I'll step down and let you guys like go at it too. So yeah
I'll let you touch it good
Yeah
So we needed someone to join
Everyone's gonna show shy though
Well, I don't know it is free
Let's change the topic. Let's just pop it then. Okay
How do you feel like we're gonna make people
You're going
How do we're gonna make that? Well, I think Nick Johnson might but then it's like he might not say very much
Well, I make Johnson fucking join. Let's run that bitch dog
Yeah, okay. So lava doesn't want to be on panel arguing. They want to argue from the chat. Oh, that's okay
Well, I don't know is it a porn bomb? It's not then let them up if it is then don't let them up
It is they said they're not up. They didn't say they're not a panel person period. Can I see them backstage or only you?
Oh, well, there's nobody backstage, but you'd be able to see like a number
I think it will say like there's somebody back stage is usually people are able to see
Do they give us or do they give us their word? They're not a porn bomber. I
Don't they were they're not there. I mean, they say they're not they're not coming on panel. Do they give us their word?
Yeah, they did they did. All right, let them drink. All right
Okay, come on. You heard Lava you can join he said you can join but it's like you be quick with it though
I know but I mean as soon as they come
There's well, there's nobody there
Hold on we do you hear we have someone debate you here you go
Ghosts
Oh my god, what's up, brother? What are you doing? Do it you chill it? Are you doing brother? Yeah, I'm chillin. How are you doing?
I'm doing good
Thank you, just like wow
I'm finna leave though. I gotta go to the movies brother. I hate the
What you gonna see what you're gonna see in the movie? Oh
Fantastic for her sir. Oh
Now I want I'm going to see the smurf. I want to see that smurf movie that little cartoon shit. You can't you come
You look like Guggamel
Yeah, oh
Yeah, I just chopped us like on for them you're yo
Yo girls, I just got punched by a female, bro
Who the fuck buy a female?
Yeah, she punched me right in my arm, bro
What the fuck, what's up? I'm running, I'm running
She just punched me, she just punched me for no reason
Is she a trans?
Nah, she ain't no damn trans
We crash out, you wanna crash out tonight? We crash out
No, ain't nobody gonna punch my boy. You're there. Nobody gonna punch you. You're
You gonna punch my boy we're gonna crash out you're
It's crazy today's bar, right? Hey, well, it's like it might be crazy. Let's crash out here
Nobody gonna punch my boy. You got me fucked up
Homegirl homegirl just walked up on her grocery cabbage
Oh
That's woman. Just miss me for no reason. I'm like a retard sir. You sound like a retard go
Who the fuck is you? Let's run that bitch dog. You want to run it? Who the fuck is you talking to you, boy?
Let me get my fucking bitch. You don't the fuck you're talking about just repeat. You know, what the fuck you're talking about
Ah, you don't like your baits
You don't like your own medicine. Let's run that bitch dog. Let's run that bitch, bro
You know one's in your let me get my ones. You're a foreign name. He heard you're falling. We heard I
Find this often to run up with you
I'm gonna run up on you. Sure
Let me get my phone one. Yeah, we're in front of heaven
Let me let me get my squabbles you heard. Yeah, we're going to heaven. Let's go
Let me get my squabbles you heard. No, no, no, we're gonna ghost. We're gonna fly to heaven. Come on. Let's go
We're going together
Yeah
No
No, no, no, let me get my squabbles in your fuck that. No, no, no, now fuck you. Let me go squabbles it
Fuck you
Well, fuck you too, then bitch. Let's run that bitch fuck you too, bitch
Yeah, let's run that bitch dog. Let's run that bitch. Yeah, let's run that bitch dog. Let's run it
Let's run it. All right, let's run it. You're fucking bitch. You don't the fuck you're talking about
I'm trying to make you fucking retard
You're fucking retard, I'm trying to make the argument you dumb fuck fuck you
That was rude. Yeah, shut
Should I should I crash out or not?
You need to go to movies watch your movies. Yeah, should I crash out or not? Yeah, bitch. You may
Go night night go go night night
Let's just say you don't know fuck you're talking about it. You're trying to
You tired nothing what you're talking about
You want to squabble up
You want to squabble you want to squabble up do you want to squabble
I don't give a fuck. Hey on camera. No camera. I beat the fuck out. Do you want to squabble it? No, you can't. No, you can't. Cam up
Do you want to squabble up? Yes or no? Cam up. Cam up, bro. Cam up. Okay. I'll cam up
Do you want to squabble up? I'll cam up. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, Cam up. Yeah, Cam up. All right, I'll fuck it. All right
Yeah, do you want to squabble it up?
Cam up. I'll beat the fuck out you boy. No, you can't. No, you can't. I'll be woofered on that boy here. How, how, how?
Well, my face against your face. That's how you try you try you try you try you want to squabble you want some squabbles
You want some squabbles?
Squabble up you heard
Squabble up you heard on four and then on four and then
Yeah
I'm putting on four and then I'll beat the fuck at you on four and then you're beat the fuck out of you you heard
Yeah, yeah, you're nothing. You're sitting here. You ain't going to your daddy. You're gonna say yes or to me
You're no, no, you don't go night night. You'll tell all right daddy. I'm going night night
Yeah
You better listen to your dad that's running up
Let's run it up from it
Let's run it up, bitch. Let's run it up. I'll beat the fuck out you. Let's run it up. Yeah, I'll beat the fuck out of you
Yeah, let me get my squabbles in
You fucking I'll make you look like a ghost. I'll make you look like a ghost
I'll make you look like a bitch. I'll make you look like butchies
I'll make you look like by the way you could never
I'll make you look like a jacket
No, no, no, you didn't
Yeah, I already won. No, no, no, you can't
I literally already won no, you can't can't beat the devil
I already won
No, you can't beat the devil boy boy
You heard boy boy
Now I have to get into another argument you realize already won right?
No, you didn't want I'm down to get back into I already won
Explain to me I'll explain to me how I'd explain to me how I didn't explain
I would go ahead
Go ahead. Hey, you repeat the words. I'm saying explain
You're too stupid to have it
Oh, you ready buddy? I was in his unit. Okay. I I you went to fee. I you went to fee
All right
I could see
Right
Appreciate you that was really fucking easy. I appreciate you though
You're gonna
Yeah, I won you heard like you just meant you heard no
Now you fucking I just won
Psychi-wiki
I'm flying where
Sikey, what you at? Sikey?
Sikey
Let's go to beat us guys.
Save psyche sent you.
Everyone go to beat us. Okay.
Hey, man.
Sorry guys.
I'll be right back.
Love you.
What's the end?
Let's see beta
Or a summer go or a hotness summer, okay? Love you guys. I'll be back tonight
See how to both of them. Love you guys